id1,affil1,affil_tokens_labeled,affil_tokens,total_entities
7927,", IBM Almaden Research Center, 650 Harry Road, CA 95120, San Jose, USA",IBM Almaden Research Center<ORG>; Harry Road<LOC>; CA 95120<LOC>; San Jose<LOC>; USA<LOC>,IBM Almaden Research Center; Harry Road; CA 95120; San Jose; USA,5
7930,", IIT Bombay",Bombay<LOC>,Bombay,1
7987,", University of California, San Diego, USA",University of California<ORG>; San Diego<LOC>; USA<LOC>,University of California; San Diego; USA,3
5613,"28msec Inc., Zurich, Switzerland",28msec Inc.<ORG>; Zurich<LOC>; Switzerland<LOC>,28msec Inc.; Zurich; Switzerland,3
9530,"28msec, Inc.","28msec, Inc<ORG>","28msec, Inc",1
7952,"76 Patision Street, Athens University of Economics and Business, Athens, Greece",Athens University of Economics and Business<ORG>; Athens<LOC>; Greece<LOC>,Athens University of Economics and Business; Athens; Greece,3
7569,Aalborg Univ.,Aalborg Univ<PER>,Aalborg Univ,1
7608,"Aalborg Univ., Aalborg, The Netherlands",Aalborg Univ<PER>; Aalborg<LOC>; The Netherlands<LOC>,Aalborg Univ; Aalborg; The Netherlands,3
946,Aalborg University,Aalborg University<ORG>,Aalborg University,1
2336,"Aalborg University, Aalborg, Denmark",Aalborg University<ORG>; Aalborg<LOC>; Denmark<LOC>,Aalborg University; Aalborg; Denmark,3
2367,"Aalborg University, Denmark",Aalborg University<ORG>; Denmark<LOC>,Aalborg University; Denmark,2
8298,"Aalborg University, Denmark, Ost, Denmark",Aalborg University<ORG>; Denmark<LOC>; Ost<LOC>,Aalborg University; Denmark; Ost,4
651,"Advanced Data Management Technologies Laboratory, Department of Computer Science, University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA",Advanced Data Management Technologies Laboratory<MISC>; Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of Pittsburgh<ORG>; Pittsburgh<LOC>; PA<LOC>,Advanced Data Management Technologies Laboratory; Department of Computer Science; University of Pittsburgh; Pittsburgh; PA,5
7572,Agricultural Univ. of Athens,Athens<LOC>,Athens,1
8865,"Alma Mater Studiorum—Università di Bologna, Bologna, Italy",Alma Mater Studiorum—<MISC>; Università di Bologna<LOC>; Bologna<LOC>; Italy<LOC>,Alma Mater Studiorum—; Università di Bologna; Bologna; Italy,4
8445,Almaden,Almaden<ORG>,Almaden,1
5887,"Almaden Research Center, San Jose, CA, USA",Research Center<LOC>; San Jose<LOC>; CA<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Research Center; San Jose; CA; USA,4
672,"Amazon Corp., Seattle",Amazon Corp<LOC>; Seattle<LOC>,Amazon Corp; Seattle,2
8128,"Amazon.com, Seattle",Amazon.com<ORG>; Seattle<LOC>,Amazon.com; Seattle,2
8425,"Applications Research Laboratory, Corporate Technology Group, Intel Corporation, USA",Applications Research Laboratory<ORG>; Corporate Technology Group<ORG>; Intel Corporation<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Applications Research Laboratory; Corporate Technology Group; Intel Corporation; USA,4
3893,"Aristotle University, Thessaloniki, Greece",Aristotle University<ORG>; Thessaloniki<LOC>; Greece<LOC>,Aristotle University; Thessaloniki; Greece,3
2341,"Arizona State Univ., Tempe, AZ",Arizona State Univ<LOC>; Tempe<LOC>; AZ<ORG>,Arizona State Univ; Tempe; AZ,3
494,"Arizona State University, Arizona",Arizona State University<ORG>; Arizona<LOC>,Arizona State University; Arizona,2
2385,"Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ",Arizona State University<ORG>; Tempe<ORG>; AZ<ORG>,Arizona State University; Tempe; AZ,3
5629,"Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ, USA",Arizona State University<ORG>; Tempe<ORG>; AZ<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Arizona State University; Tempe; AZ; USA,4
9469,"Arizona State University, Tempe, USA",Arizona State University<ORG>; Tempe<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Arizona State University; Tempe; USA,3
3068,Aster Data,Aster Data<ORG>,Aster Data,1
9563,Aster Data Systems,Aster Data Systems<ORG>,Aster Data Systems,1
5130,"ASU, Tempe, AZ",ASU<ORG>; Tempe<ORG>; AZ<ORG>,ASU; Tempe; AZ,3
4046,AT & T Labs-Research,AT & T Labs-Research<ORG>,AT & T Labs-Research,1
4168,"AT & T Labs-Research, Florham Park, NJ",AT & T Labs-Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,AT & T Labs-Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
9264,"AT & T Labs-Research, Florham Park, USA 07932",AT & T Labs-Research<ORG>; Florham Park<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT & T Labs-Research; Florham Park; USA,3
3435,AT&T,AT&T<LOC>,AT&T,1
6808,AT&T Laboratories,AT&T Laboratories<ORG>,AT&T Laboratories,1
6259,"AT&T Laboratories - Research, Florham Park, NJ, USA",AT&T Laboratories - Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Laboratories - Research; Florham Park; NJ; USA,4
1635,AT&T Labs,AT&T Labs<ORG>,AT&T Labs,1
1702,AT&T Labs - Research,AT&T Labs - Research<ORG>,AT&T Labs - Research,1
4264,"AT&T Labs - Research, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Labs - Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs - Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
5865,"AT&T Labs - Research, Florham Park, NJ, USA",AT&T Labs - Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs - Research; Florham Park; NJ; USA,4
7429,AT&T Labs -- Research,AT&T Labs -- Research<ORG>,AT&T Labs -- Research,1
7761,"AT&T Labs &ndash;&#8211; Research, 180 Park Avenue, Bldg 103, Florham Park, NJ 07932, USA; E-mail: divesh@research.att.com",AT&T Labs &ndash;&#8211; Research<ORG>; Bldg 103<LOC>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ 07932<LOC>; USA<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>; divesh@research.att.com<ORG>,AT&T Labs &ndash;&#8211; Research; Bldg 103; Florham Park; NJ 07932; USA; E-mail; divesh@research.att.com,7
2240,AT&T Labs Inc.,AT&T Labs Inc<ORG>,AT&T Labs Inc,1
6367,"AT&T Labs Inc. - Research, Florham Park, NJ, USA",AT&T Labs Inc<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs Inc; Florham Park; NJ; USA,4
454,AT&T Labs Research,AT&T Labs Research<ORG>,AT&T Labs Research,1
7730,"AT&T Labs Research, 180 Park Avenue, Room E243, Florham Park, NJ 07932, USA; E-mail: mff@research.att.com",AT&T Labs Research<ORG>; Room E243<LOC>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ 07932<LOC>; USA<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>,AT&T Labs Research; Room E243; Florham Park; NJ 07932; USA; E-mail,6
7699,"AT&T Labs Research, Florham Park, N.J., USA; e-mail: divesh@research.att.com",AT&T Labs Research<ORG>; Florham Park<LOC>; N.J.<LOC>; USA<LOC>; divesh@research.att.com<ORG>,AT&T Labs Research; Florham Park; N.J.; USA; divesh@research.att.com,5
1072,"AT&T Labs Research, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Labs Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
5996,"AT&T Labs Research, Florham Park, NJ, USA",AT&T Labs Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs Research; Florham Park; NJ; USA,4
7733,AT&T Labs Research; E-mail: suciu@research.att.com,AT&T Labs Research<ORG>; E-mail<MISC>; suciu@research.att.com<MISC>,AT&T Labs Research; E-mail; suciu@research.att.com,3
7080,AT&T Labs---Research,AT&T Labs---Research<ORG>,AT&T Labs---Research,1
7659,"AT&T Labs---Research, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Labs---Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs---Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
3142,AT&T Labs--Research,AT&T Labs--Research<ORG>,AT&T Labs--Research,1
3117,"AT&T Labs--Research, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Labs--Research<ORG>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs--Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
8034,"AT&T Labs--Research, NJ",AT&T Labs--Research<ORG>; NJ<ORG>,AT&T Labs--Research; NJ,2
8024,"AT&T Labs--Research, USA",AT&T Labs--Research<ORG>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs--Research; USA,2
103,AT&T Labs-Research,AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>,AT&T Labs-Research,1
7737,"AT&T Labs-Research, 180 Park Ave., Room E 233, Florham Park, NJ 07932-0971, USA; http://www.research.att.com/~suciu",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; Room E 233<MISC>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ<MISC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs-Research; Room E 233; Florham Park; NJ; USA,5
7710,"AT&T Labs-Research, 180 Park Avenue, Bldg. 103, Florham Park, NJ 07932, USA; e-mail: {sihem, divesh}@research.att.com",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; Bldg<LOC>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ 07932<LOC>; USA<LOC>; divesh}@research.att.com<ORG>,AT&T Labs-Research; Bldg; Florham Park; NJ 07932; USA; divesh}@research.att.com,6
8948,"AT&T Labs-Research, Florham Park NJ",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; Florham Park NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs-Research; Florham Park NJ,2
2964,"AT&T Labs-Research, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs-Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
5773,"AT&T Labs-Research, New Jersey, NJ, USA",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; New Jersey<LOC>; NJ<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs-Research; New Jersey; NJ; USA,4
1456,"AT&T Labs-Research, NJ",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; NJ<ORG>,AT&T Labs-Research; NJ,2
8577,"AT&T Labs-Research, USA",AT&T Labs-Research<ORG>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs-Research; USA,2
9240,"AT&T Labs, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Labs<LOC>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Labs; Florham Park; NJ,3
6156,"AT&T Labs, Florham Park, NJ, USA",AT&T Labs<LOC>; Florham Park<LOC>; NJ<LOC>; USA<LOC>,AT&T Labs; Florham Park; NJ; USA,4
6764,"AT&T Labs, Research",AT&T Labs<ORG>,AT&T Labs,1
7624,AT&T Labs?Research,Labs?Research<MISC>,Labs?Research,1
9400,"AT&T Labs&mdash;&#8212;Research, Florham Park, NJ",Florham Park<LOC>; NJ<LOC>,Florham Park; NJ,2
7112,AT&T Research,AT&T Research<ORG>,AT&T Research,1
7105,"AT&T Research Laboratory, Florham Park, NJ",AT&T Research Laboratory<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,AT&T Research Laboratory; Florham Park; NJ,3
3074,Athens Univ. of Economics and Business,Athens Univ<LOC>; Economics and Business<MISC>,Athens Univ; Economics and Business,2
5179,"Athens University of Economics and Business, Athens, Greece",Athens University of Economics and Business<ORG>; Athens<LOC>; Greece<LOC>,Athens University of Economics and Business; Athens; Greece,3
2494,"Athens University of Economics and Business, Greece",Athens University of Economics and Business<ORG>; Greece<LOC>,Athens University of Economics and Business; Greece,2
5204,"ATT Labs - Research, Florham Park, NJ",ATT Labs - Research<ORG>; Florham Park<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,ATT Labs - Research; Florham Park; NJ,3
1854,"Basic Research Unit, Helsinki Institute for Information Technology, Department of Computer Science, University of Helsinki, Finland",Basic Research Unit<MISC>; Helsinki Institute for Information Technology<ORG>; Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of Helsinki<ORG>; Finland<LOC>,Basic Research Unit; Helsinki Institute for Information Technology; Department of Computer Science; University of Helsinki; Finland,5
1140,"Bayerisches Forschungszentrum für Wissensbasierte Systeme, Orleansstrá, München, Germany",Bayerisches Forschungszentrum für Wissensbasierte Systeme<ORG>; Orleansstrá<LOC>; München<LOC>; Germany<LOC>,Bayerisches Forschungszentrum für Wissensbasierte Systeme; Orleansstrá; München; Germany,4
3653,BEA Systems,BEA Systems<ORG>,BEA Systems,1
6321,"BEA Systems Inc, San Jose, CA, USA",BEA Systems Inc<ORG>; San Jose<LOC>; CA<LOC>; USA<LOC>,BEA Systems Inc; San Jose; CA; USA,4
2587,"BEA Systems, Inc, San Jose","BEA Systems, Inc<ORG>; San Jose<LOC>","BEA Systems, Inc; San Jose",2
2465,"BEA Systems, Inc.",BEA Systems<ORG>,BEA Systems,1
1224,"BEA Systems, Inc.,",BEA Systems<ORG>,BEA Systems,1
4616,"BEA Systems, Inc., Burlington, MA",BEA Systems<ORG>; Burlington<LOC>; MA<LOC>,BEA Systems; Burlington; MA,3
5337,"BEA Systems, Inc., San Francisco, CA",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Francisco<LOC>; CA<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Francisco; CA,3
799,"BEA Systems, Inc., San Jose, CA",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Jose<LOC>; CA<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Jose; CA,3
804,"BEA Systems, Inc., San Jose, CA and Computer Science Department at the University of California, San Diego",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Jose<LOC>; CA and Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; San Diego<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Jose; CA and Computer Science Department; University of California; San Diego,5
4627,"BEA Systems, Liberty Corner, NJ",BEA Systems<ORG>; Liberty Corner<ORG>; NJ<LOC>,BEA Systems; Liberty Corner; NJ,3
9233,"BEA Systems, Redwood Shores, CA",BEA Systems<ORG>; Redwood Shores<ORG>; CA<ORG>,BEA Systems; Redwood Shores; CA,3
4629,"BEA Systems, San Francisco, CA",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Francisco<LOC>; CA<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Francisco; CA,3
1583,"BEA Systems, San Jose, CA",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Jose<LOC>; CA<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Jose; CA,3
1585,"BEA Systems, San Jose, CA and Technical University of Munich, Munich, Germany",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Jose<LOC>; CA and<ORG>; Technical University of Munich<ORG>; Munich<LOC>; Germany<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Jose; CA and; Technical University of Munich; Munich; Germany,6
8070,"BEA Systems, USA",BEA Systems<ORG>; USA<LOC>,BEA Systems; USA,2
4236,"BEA Systems. Inc., San Francisco, CA",BEA Systems<ORG>; San Francisco<LOC>; CA<LOC>,BEA Systems; San Francisco; CA,3
3,Bell Laboratories,Bell Laboratories<ORG>,Bell Laboratories,1
100,Bell Laboratories (India),Bell Laboratories<ORG>; India<LOC>,Bell Laboratories; India,2
6511,"Bell Laboratories, 600 Mountain Avenue, Murray Hill, NJ",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Mountain Avenue<LOC>; Murray Hill<LOC>; NJ<MISC>,Bell Laboratories; Mountain Avenue; Murray Hill; NJ,4
7861,"Bell Laboratories, 600 Mountain Avenue, Murray Hill, NJ 07974, USA; e-mail: {minos,rastogi}@bell-labs.com","Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Mountain Avenue<LOC>; Murray Hill<LOC>; NJ 07974<LOC>; USA<LOC>; minos,rastogi}@bell-labs.com<ORG>","Bell Laboratories; Mountain Avenue; Murray Hill; NJ 07974; USA; minos,rastogi}@bell-labs.com",6
5671,"Bell Laboratories, Alcatel-Lucent, Lisle, IL, USA",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Alcatel-Lucent<ORG>; Lisle<LOC>; IL<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Bell Laboratories; Alcatel-Lucent; Lisle; IL; USA,5
22,"Bell Laboratories, Lucent Technologies",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>,Bell Laboratories; Lucent Technologies,2
7913,"Bell Laboratories, Lucent Technologies, 600 Mountain Ave., NJ 07974, Murray Hill, USA",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>; NJ 07974<MISC>; Murray Hill<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Bell Laboratories; Lucent Technologies; NJ 07974; Murray Hill; USA,5
7717,"Bell Laboratories, Lucent Technologies, 600 Mountain Ave., NJ 07974, USA; {cychan, pascal, minos, rastogi}@research.bell-labs.com",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>; NJ 07974<LOC>; USA<LOC>; pascal<PER>; minos<PER>; rastogi}@research.bell-labs.com<MISC>,Bell Laboratories; Lucent Technologies; NJ 07974; USA; pascal; minos; rastogi}@research.bell-labs.com,7
7320,"Bell Laboratories, Lucent Technologies, Murray Hill, NJ",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>; Murray Hill<PER>; NJ<MISC>,Bell Laboratories; Lucent Technologies; Murray Hill; NJ,4
8098,"Bell Laboratories, Lucent Technologies, USA",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Bell Laboratories; Lucent Technologies; USA,3
6586,"Bell Laboratories, Murray Hill, NJ",Bell Laboratories<ORG>; Murray Hill<PER>; NJ<MISC>,Bell Laboratories; Murray Hill; NJ,3
455,Bell Labs,Bell Labs<ORG>,Bell Labs,1
4330,Bell Labs Research,Bell Labs Research<ORG>,Bell Labs Research,1
5591,"Bell Labs Research India, India",Bell Labs Research India<ORG>; India<LOC>,Bell Labs Research India; India,2
5655,"Bell Labs Research, Bangalore, India",Bell Labs Research<ORG>; Bangalore<LOC>; India<LOC>,Bell Labs Research; Bangalore; India,3
2246,"Bell Labs, Alcatel-Lucent",Bell Labs<ORG>; Alcatel-Lucent<ORG>,Bell Labs; Alcatel-Lucent,2
7007,"Bell Labs, Lucent",Bell Labs<ORG>,Bell Labs,1
1,"Bell Labs, Lucent Technologies",Bell Labs<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>,Bell Labs; Lucent Technologies,2
7120,"Bell Labs, Lucent Technologies Murray Hill, NJ",Bell Labs<ORG>; Lucent Technologies Murray Hill<ORG>; NJ<MISC>,Bell Labs; Lucent Technologies Murray Hill; NJ,3
7999,"Bell Labs, Lucent Technologies, Murray Hill, New Jersey",Bell Labs<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>; Murray Hill<LOC>; New Jersey<LOC>,Bell Labs; Lucent Technologies; Murray Hill; New Jersey,4
8206,"Bell Labs, Lucent Technologies, Murray Hill, NJ",Bell Labs<ORG>; Lucent Technologies<ORG>; Murray Hill<PER>; NJ<MISC>,Bell Labs; Lucent Technologies; Murray Hill; NJ,4
6487,"Bell Labs, Murray Hill, NJ",Bell Labs<ORG>; Murray Hill<PER>; NJ<MISC>,Bell Labs; Murray Hill; NJ,3
6538,Bell Labs.,Bell Labs<ORG>,Bell Labs,1
543,Berkeley,Berkeley<PER>,Berkeley,1
4052,Berufsakademie Stuttgart/IBM Germany,IBM Germany<ORG>,IBM Germany,1
8106,"Bilkent University, Ankara, Turkey",Bilkent University<ORG>; Ankara<LOC>; Turkey<LOC>,Bilkent University; Ankara; Turkey,3
8108,"Bilkent University, Bursa, Turkey",Bilkent University<ORG>; Bursa<LOC>; Turkey<LOC>,Bilkent University; Bursa; Turkey,3
321,"Biological Data Management and Technology Center, Berkeley, CA",Biological Data Management and Technology Center<MISC>; Berkeley<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Biological Data Management and Technology Center; Berkeley; CA,3
4246,Boeing Phantom Works,Boeing Phantom Works<MISC>,Boeing Phantom Works,1
257,Boston University,Boston University<ORG>,Boston University,1
2331,"Boston University, Boston, MA",Boston University<ORG>; Boston<ORG>; MA<LOC>,Boston University; Boston; MA,3
5642,"Boston University, Boston, MA, USA",Boston University<ORG>; Boston<LOC>; MA<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Boston University; Boston; MA; USA,4
9373,"Boston University, Boston, USA",Boston University<ORG>; Boston<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Boston University; Boston; USA,3
9383,"Boston University, Boston, USA 02215",Boston University<ORG>; Boston<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Boston University; Boston; USA,3
155,"Brandeis University, Waltham, MA",Brandeis University<ORG>; Waltham<ORG>; MA<LOC>,Brandeis University; Waltham; MA,3
5706,"Brandeis University, Waltham, MA, USA",Brandeis University<ORG>; Waltham<ORG>; MA<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Brandeis University; Waltham; MA; USA,4
9625,Brown U,Brown U<MISC>,Brown U,1
736,Brown University,Brown University<ORG>,Brown University,1
164,"Brown University, Providence, RI",Brown University<ORG>; Providence<ORG>; RI<ORG>,Brown University; Providence; RI,3
5999,"Brown University, Providence, RI, USA",Brown University<ORG>; Providence<ORG>; RI<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Brown University; Providence; RI; USA,4
4644,"Brown University, Providence, RI.",Brown University<ORG>; Providence<ORG>; RI<ORG>,Brown University; Providence; RI,3
9063,C.M.U.,C.M.U.<ORG>,C.M.U.,1
1098,"C&C Research Laboratories - Silicon Valley, NEC USA, INC., Cupertino, California",C&C Research Laboratories - Silicon Valley<ORG>; NEC USA<ORG>; INC<ORG>; Cupertino<LOC>; California<LOC>,C&C Research Laboratories - Silicon Valley; NEC USA; INC; Cupertino; California,5
1244,"C&C Research Laboratories - Silicon Valley, NEC USA, Inc., Suite, Cupertino, California",C&C Research Laboratories - Silicon Valley<ORG>; NEC USA<ORG>; Suite<LOC>; Cupertino<LOC>; California<LOC>,C&C Research Laboratories - Silicon Valley; NEC USA; Suite; Cupertino; California,5
7777,"C&C Research Laboratories, NEC USA, 110 Rio Robles, M/S SJ100, San Jose, CA 95134, USA; E-mail: {wen,candan,hirata,hara}@ccrl.sj.nec.com",C&C Research Laboratories<ORG>; NEC USA<ORG>; Rio Robles<LOC>; M<LOC>; S SJ100<LOC>; San Jose<LOC>; CA 95134<LOC>; USA<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>,C&C Research Laboratories; NEC USA; Rio Robles; M; S SJ100; San Jose; CA 95134; USA; E-mail,9
6883,"C&C Research Laboratories, NEC, Inc., 110 Rio Robles, San Jose, CA",C&C Research Laboratories<ORG>; NEC<ORG>; Rio Robles<LOC>; San Jose<LOC>; CA<LOC>,C&C Research Laboratories; NEC; Rio Robles; San Jose; CA,5
9792,"Carnegie Mellon University, 5000 Forbes Ave., Pittsburgh, PA 15213, USA",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Forbes Ave<ORG>; Pittsburgh<LOC>; PA 15213<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Carnegie Mellon University; Forbes Ave; Pittsburgh; PA 15213; USA,5
9040,"Carnegie Mellon University, Akamai Technologies",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Akamai Technologies<ORG>,Carnegie Mellon University; Akamai Technologies,2
9039,"Carnegie Mellon University, EPFL",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; EPFL<ORG>,Carnegie Mellon University; EPFL,2
9041,"Carnegie Mellon University, Intel Research Pittsburgh",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Intel Research Pittsburgh<ORG>,Carnegie Mellon University; Intel Research Pittsburgh,2
4139,"Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Pittsburgh<ORG>,Carnegie Mellon University; Pittsburgh,2
18,"Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Pittsburgh<ORG>; PA<LOC>,Carnegie Mellon University; Pittsburgh; PA,3
5598,"Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA, USA",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Pittsburgh<LOC>; PA<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Carnegie Mellon University; Pittsburgh; PA; USA,4
896,"Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Pittsburgh<LOC>; Pennsylvania<LOC>,Carnegie Mellon University; Pittsburgh; Pennsylvania,3
8064,"Carnegie Mellon University, USA",Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Carnegie Mellon University; USA,2
32,"Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, OH",Case Western Reserve University<ORG>; Cleveland<ORG>; OH<ORG>,Case Western Reserve University; Cleveland; OH,3
1651,Cedric-CNAM,Cedric-CNAM<ORG>,Cedric-CNAM,1
2691,"CEDRIC-CNAM Paris, France",CEDRIC-<MISC>; France<LOC>,CEDRIC-; France,2
9413,"Cedric, CNAM, Paris, France",Cedric<ORG>; CNAM<ORG>; Paris<LOC>; France<LOC>,Cedric; CNAM; Paris; France,4
7680,"Cedric/CNAM Paris, France; e-mail: vodislav&commat;cnam.fr",Cedric<ORG>; CNAM Paris<ORG>; France<LOC>,Cedric; CNAM Paris; France,3
1416,"Center for Adv. Compu. Studies, Univ. of Louisiana at Lafayette, Lafayette, LA",Adv<LOC>; Compu<LOC>; Studies<LOC>; Univ<LOC>; Louisiana<LOC>; Lafayette<LOC>; LA<LOC>,Adv; Compu; Studies; Univ; Louisiana; Lafayette; LA,8
8057,"Center for Advanced Computer Studies, University of Illinois at Chicago, USA",University of Illinois<ORG>; Chicago<LOC>; USA<LOC>,University of Illinois; Chicago; USA,3
9428,"Center for Comprehensive Informatics, Emory University, Atlanta, USA 30322",Emory University<ORG>; Atlanta<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Emory University; Atlanta; USA,3
883,"Center for Research in Biological System, University of California, San Diego, CA",Center for Research in Biological System<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; San Diego<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Center for Research in Biological System; University of California; San Diego; CA,4
2224,"Centrum voor Wiskunde en Informatica, Amsterdam, the Netherlands",Wiskunde<LOC>; Informatica<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; Netherlands<LOC>,Wiskunde; Informatica; Amsterdam; Netherlands,4
7082,"Centrum voor Wiskunde en Informatica, Kruislaan 413, 1098 SJ, Amsterdam, The Netherlands",Wiskunde<LOC>; Informatica<LOC>; Kruislaan<LOC>; SJ<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; The Netherlands<LOC>,Wiskunde; Informatica; Kruislaan; SJ; Amsterdam; The Netherlands,6
2408,"Centrum voor Wiskunde en Informatica, SJ Amsterdam, The Netherlands",Wiskunde<LOC>; SJ Amsterdam<ORG>; The Netherlands<ORG>,Wiskunde; SJ Amsterdam; The Netherlands,3
6118,"Centrum Wiskunde en Informatica, Amsterdam, Netherlands",Centrum Wiskunde<LOC>; Informatica<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; Netherlands<LOC>,Centrum Wiskunde; Informatica; Amsterdam; Netherlands,4
2095,"CERIA Lab., Université Paris Dauphine, France",CERIA Lab<MISC>; Université Paris Dauphine<ORG>; France<LOC>,CERIA Lab; Université Paris Dauphine; France,3
8769,"CERIAS and Department of Computer Science, Purdue University, West Lafayette, USA",CERIAS<MISC>; Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Purdue University<ORG>; West Lafayette<LOC>; USA<LOC>,CERIAS; Department of Computer Science; Purdue University; West Lafayette; USA,5
7156,CERN,CERN<LOC>,CERN,1
1027,"CES Dept., UC Riverside",CES Dept<ORG>; UC Riverside<ORG>,CES Dept; UC Riverside,2
2583,"Chinese Academy of Sciences, Beijing, China",Chinese Academy of Sciences<ORG>; Beijing<LOC>; China<LOC>,Chinese Academy of Sciences; Beijing; China,3
9641,"Chinese Academy of Sciences, China",Chinese Academy of Sciences<ORG>; China<LOC>,Chinese Academy of Sciences; China,2
8992,"Chinese university of Hong Kong, Hong Kong, China",Chinese<MISC>; Hong Kong<LOC>; China<LOC>,Chinese; Hong Kong; China,4
5280,"Chinese University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong, Hong Kong",Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Chinese University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong,3
3223,"Chinese University of Hong Kong, New Territories, Hong Kong",Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; New Territories<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Chinese University of Hong Kong; New Territories; Hong Kong,3
9136,"Chinese University of Hong Kong, Sha Tin, New Territories, Hong Kong",Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Sha Tin<LOC>; New Territories<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Chinese University of Hong Kong; Sha Tin; New Territories; Hong Kong,4
3905,Chutney Technologies,Chutney Technologies<ORG>,Chutney Technologies,1
8037,"Chutney Technologies, Atlanta, GA",Chutney Technologies<ORG>; Atlanta<ORG>; GA<ORG>,Chutney Technologies; Atlanta; GA,3
6972,"Chutney Technologies, Inc., Atlanta, GA",Chutney Technologies<ORG>; Atlanta<LOC>; GA<ORG>,Chutney Technologies; Atlanta; GA,3
7795,"CIMIC and MSIS Department, Rutgers University, 180 University Avenue, Newark NJ 07102, USA e-mail: adam@adam.rutgers.edu; atluri@andromeda.rutgers.edu",CIMIC<ORG>; MSIS Department<ORG>; Rutgers University<ORG>; University Avenue<ORG>; Newark NJ 07102<LOC>; USA<LOC>,CIMIC; MSIS Department; Rutgers University; University Avenue; Newark NJ 07102; USA,6
1348,"CIS Department, Polytechnic University, Brooklyn, NY",CIS Department<ORG>; Polytechnic University<ORG>; Brooklyn<LOC>; NY<LOC>,CIS Department; Polytechnic University; Brooklyn; NY,4
763,"CISE Department, University of Florida, Gainesville, FL",CISE Department<ORG>; University of Florida<ORG>; Gainesville<LOC>; FL<LOC>,CISE Department; University of Florida; Gainesville; FL,4
4814,City University of Hong Kong,City University of Hong Kong<ORG>,City University of Hong Kong,1
75,"City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong",City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,City University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong,2
7890,"City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong, China",City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>; China<LOC>,City University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong; China,3
9292,"City University of Hong Kong, Kowloon, Hong Kong",City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,City University of Hong Kong; Kowloon; Hong Kong,3
9284,"Clausthal University of Technology, Clausthal-Zellerfeld, Germany",Clausthal University of Technology<ORG>; Clausthal-Zellerfeld<LOC>; Germany<LOC>,Clausthal University of Technology; Clausthal-Zellerfeld; Germany,3
3862,Clustra AS,Clustra AS<ORG>,Clustra AS,1
3487,"Clustra, Trondheim, Norway",Clustra<LOC>; Trondheim<LOC>; Norway<LOC>,Clustra; Trondheim; Norway,3
3406,CMU,CMU<ORG>,CMU,1
3561,CNAM,CNAM<ORG>,CNAM,1
3763,CNAM Paris,CNAM Paris<ORG>,CNAM Paris,1
2872,"CNAM, France",CNAM<ORG>; France<LOC>,CNAM; France,2
691,"College of Computer and Information Science, Northeastern University, Boston, MA",College of Computer and Information Science<ORG>; Northeastern University<ORG>; Boston<ORG>; MA<LOC>,College of Computer and Information Science; Northeastern University; Boston; MA,4
8176,"College of Computer and Information Science, Northeastern University, USA",College of Computer and Information Science<ORG>; Northeastern University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,College of Computer and Information Science; Northeastern University; USA,3
6634,"College of Computing, Georgia Institute of Technology",College of Computing<ORG>; Georgia Institute of Technology<ORG>,College of Computing; Georgia Institute of Technology,2
7960,"College of Computing, Georgia Institute of Technology, 801 Atlantic Drive, GA, 30332-0280, Atlanta, USA",College of Computing<ORG>; Georgia Institute of Technology<ORG>; Atlantic Drive<MISC>; GA<ORG>; Atlanta<LOC>; USA<LOC>,College of Computing; Georgia Institute of Technology; Atlantic Drive; GA; Atlanta; USA,6
1211,"College of Engineering, School of Computer Engineering, Nanyang Technological University, Singapore",College of Engineering<ORG>; School of Computer Engineering<ORG>; Nanyang Technological University<ORG>; Singapore<LOC>,College of Engineering; School of Computer Engineering; Nanyang Technological University; Singapore,4
7880,"College of Information Science and Technology, Drexel University, 3141 Chestnut Street, Philadelphia, PA 19104-2875, USA",College of Information Science and Technology<ORG>; Drexel University<ORG>; Chestnut Street<LOC>; Philadelphia<LOC>; PA 19104-2875<LOC>; USA<LOC>,College of Information Science and Technology; Drexel University; Chestnut Street; Philadelphia; PA 19104-2875; USA,6
1161,"College of Information Science and Technology, Drexel University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania",College of Information Science and Technology<ORG>; Drexel University<ORG>; Philadelphia<LOC>; Pennsylvania<LOC>,College of Information Science and Technology; Drexel University; Philadelphia; Pennsylvania,4
8545,"College of Information Science and Technology, Drexel University, Philadelphia, USA 19104",College of Information Science and Technology<ORG>; Drexel University<ORG>; Philadelphia<LOC>; USA<LOC>,College of Information Science and Technology; Drexel University; Philadelphia; USA,4
861,"College of Information Sciences and Technology, The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA",College of Information Sciences and Technology<ORG>; The Pennsylvania State University<ORG>; University Park<ORG>; PA<ORG>,College of Information Sciences and Technology; The Pennsylvania State University; University Park; PA,4
865,"College of Information Sciences and Technology, The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA and Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA",College of Information Sciences and Technology<ORG>; The Pennsylvania State University<ORG>; University Park<ORG>; PA<ORG>; Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>,College of Information Sciences and Technology; The Pennsylvania State University; University Park; PA; Department of Computer Science and Engineering,8
9237,"Columbia University, New York",Columbia University<ORG>; New York<LOC>,Columbia University; New York,2
8004,"Columbia University, New York, New York",Columbia University<ORG>; New York<LOC>,Columbia University; New York,3
479,"Columbia University, New York, NY",Columbia University<ORG>; New York<LOC>; NY<LOC>,Columbia University; New York; NY,3
6026,"Columbia University, New York, NY, USA",Columbia University<ORG>; New York<LOC>; NY<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Columbia University; New York; NY; USA,4
2935,"Columbia University, NYC, NY",Columbia University<ORG>; NYC<ORG>; NY<LOC>,Columbia University; NYC; NY,3
968,"Comp. Eng. Dept, Bilkent University, Ankara, Turkey",Comp<PER>; Bilkent University<ORG>; Ankara<LOC>; Turkey<LOC>,Comp; Bilkent University; Ankara; Turkey,4
1503,"Comp. Sci. Div, Dept EECS, UC Berkeley, Berkeley, CA",Comp<PER>; Dept EECS<MISC>; UC Berkeley<ORG>; Berkeley<ORG>; CA<ORG>,Comp; Dept EECS; UC Berkeley; Berkeley; CA,5
6483,"Compaq SRC, Palo Alto, CA",Compaq SRC<ORG>; Palo Alto<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Compaq SRC; Palo Alto; CA,3
7580,Compaq Systems Research Center,Compaq Systems Research Center<ORG>,Compaq Systems Research Center,1
3497,"Compaq, Il, USA",Compaq<ORG>; Il<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Compaq; Il; USA,3
6752,"Computer & Information Science Department, University of Pennsylvania, 200 South 33rd Street, Philadelphia, PA",Computer & Information Science Department<ORG>; University of Pennsylvania<ORG>; South 33rd Street<LOC>; Philadelphia<LOC>; PA<LOC>,Computer & Information Science Department; University of Pennsylvania; South 33rd Street; Philadelphia; PA,5
9267,"Computer and Information Science and Engineering Department, University of Florida, Gainesville, USA 32611",Computer and Information Science and Engineering Department<MISC>; University of Florida<ORG>; Gainesville<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer and Information Science and Engineering Department; University of Florida; Gainesville; USA,4
8795,"Computer and Information Science and Engineering, University of Florida, Gainesville, USA 32611",Computer and Information Science and Engineering<MISC>; University of Florida<ORG>; Gainesville<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer and Information Science and Engineering; University of Florida; Gainesville; USA,4
7881,"Computer Engineering and Informatics, University of Patras, Greece",Computer Engineering and Informatics<ORG>; University of Patras<ORG>; Greece<LOC>,Computer Engineering and Informatics; University of Patras; Greece,3
1925,"Computer Laboratory, University of Cambridge",Computer Laboratory<ORG>; University of Cambridge<ORG>,Computer Laboratory; University of Cambridge,2
2075,"Computer Science & Engineering Department, University of California, Riverside, Riverside, CA",Computer Science & Engineering Department<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Computer Science & Engineering Department; University of California; Riverside; CA,5
1126,"Computer Science & Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology, Mumbai, India",Computer Science & Engineering<ORG>; Indian Institute of Technology<ORG>; Mumbai<LOC>; India<LOC>,Computer Science & Engineering; Indian Institute of Technology; Mumbai; India,4
2176,"Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Lab., Massachusetts Institute of Technology",Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Lab<ORG>; Massachusetts Institute of Technology<ORG>,Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Lab; Massachusetts Institute of Technology,2
1292,"Computer Science and Engg. Dept., I.I.T., Bombay",Computer Science and Engg<ORG>; Dept<MISC>; I.I.T.<ORG>; Bombay<LOC>,Computer Science and Engg; Dept; I.I.T.; Bombay,4
6477,"Computer Science and Engg., Tndian Institiue of Technology, Mumbai 400076,INDIA",Computer Science and Engg<ORG>; Tndian Institiue of Technology<MISC>; Mumbai<LOC>,Computer Science and Engg; Tndian Institiue of Technology; Mumbai,3
7744,"Computer Science and Engineering Department, Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ 85287-5406, USA; e-mail: candan@asu.edu",Computer Science and Engineering Department<ORG>; Arizona State University<ORG>; Tempe<ORG>; AZ<ORG>; USA<LOC>; candan@asu.edu<MISC>,Computer Science and Engineering Department; Arizona State University; Tempe; AZ; USA; candan@asu.edu,6
8823,"Computer Science and Engineering Department, State University of New York at Buffalo, Amherst, USA 14260",Computer Science and Engineering Department<ORG>; State University of New York<ORG>; Buffalo<LOC>; Amherst<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science and Engineering Department; State University of New York; Buffalo; Amherst; USA,5
7892,"Computer Science and Engineering Department, University of California, Riverside, CA",Computer Science and Engineering Department<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Computer Science and Engineering Department; University of California; Riverside; CA,4
8868,"Computer Science and Engineering, Arizona State University, Tempe, USA",Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Arizona State University<ORG>; Tempe<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science and Engineering; Arizona State University; Tempe; USA,4
6519,Computer Science Department Carnegie Mellon University,Computer Science Department Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>,Computer Science Department Carnegie Mellon University,1
8338,"Computer Science Department, Boston University, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Boston University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Boston University; USA,3
1824,"Computer Science Department, Brown University",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Brown University<ORG>,Computer Science Department; Brown University,2
943,"Computer Science Department, Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Pittsburgh<ORG>,Computer Science Department; Carnegie Mellon University; Pittsburgh,3
1462,"Computer Science Department, Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; Pittsburgh<ORG>; PA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Carnegie Mellon University; Pittsburgh; PA,4
8062,"Computer Science Department, Carnegie Mellon University, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Carnegie Mellon University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Carnegie Mellon University; USA,3
1451,"Computer Science Department, Center for Automation Research and Institute for Advanced Computer Studies, University of Maryland at College Park",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Center for Automation Research and<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Center for Automation Research and; University of Maryland; College Park,4
7805,"Computer Science Department, Center for Automation Research, and Institute for Advanced Computer Studies, University of Maryland, College Park, Maryland 20742, USA; e-mail: hjs&commat;cs.umd.edu",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Center for Automation Research<ORG>; Institute for Advanced Computer Studies<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<LOC>; Maryland<LOC>; USA<LOC>; hjs&commat;cs.umd.edu<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Center for Automation Research; Institute for Advanced Computer Studies; University of Maryland; College Park; Maryland; USA; hjs&commat;cs.umd.edu,8
6957,"Computer Science Department, Columbia University",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Columbia University<ORG>,Computer Science Department; Columbia University,2
7942,"Computer Science Department, Duke University, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Duke University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Duke University; USA,3
1810,"Computer Science Department, Hong Kong Univ. of Science and Technology, Hong Kong",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Hong Kong Univ<LOC>; Science and Technology<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Hong Kong Univ; Science and Technology; Hong Kong,4
8588,"Computer Science Department, Illinois Institute of Technology, Chicago, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Illinois Institute of Technology<ORG>; Chicago<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Illinois Institute of Technology; Chicago; USA,4
842,"Computer Science Department, Indiana University, Bloomington",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Indiana University<ORG>; Bloomington<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Indiana University; Bloomington,3
7857,"Computer Science Department, Stanford University, Stanford, CA 94305, USA; E-mail: hector@db.stanford.edu",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Stanford University<ORG>; Stanford<ORG>; CA 94305<LOC>; USA<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>,Computer Science Department; Stanford University; Stanford; CA 94305; USA; E-mail,6
6866,"Computer Science Department, TECHNION - Israel Institute of Technology, Technion City, Haifa 32000, Israel",Computer Science Department<ORG>; TECHNION - Israel Institute of Technology<ORG>; Technion City<LOC>; Haifa 32000<LOC>; Israel<LOC>,Computer Science Department; TECHNION - Israel Institute of Technology; Technion City; Haifa 32000; Israel,5
8766,"Computer Science Department, Technion--Israel Institute of Technology, Haifa, Israel",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Technion<ORG>; Israel Institute of Technology<ORG>; Haifa<LOC>; Israel<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Technion; Israel Institute of Technology; Haifa; Israel,5
7815,"Computer Science Department, Tel Aviv University, Ramat Aviv, Tel Aviv 69978, Israel; E-mail: {anate, milo}@math.tau.ac.il",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Tel Aviv University<ORG>; Ramat Aviv<LOC>; Tel Aviv<LOC>; Israel<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>,Computer Science Department; Tel Aviv University; Ramat Aviv; Tel Aviv; Israel; E-mail,6
8125,"Computer Science Department, University of Arizona, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Arizona<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Arizona; USA,3
1964,"Computer Science Department, University of California, Berkeley, CA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; Berkeley<ORG>; CA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of California; Berkeley; CA,4
7715,"Computer Science Department, University of California, Riverside, California 92521, USA; e-mail: tsotras@cs.ucr.edu",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; California<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of California; Riverside; California; USA,5
8337,"Computer Science Department, University of California, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of California; USA,3
9260,"Computer Science Department, University of Illinois, Chicago, USA 60607",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Illinois<ORG>; Chicago<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Illinois; Chicago; USA,4
6924,"Computer Science Department, University of Maryland, College Park, Maryland",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<LOC>; Maryland<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Maryland; College Park; Maryland,4
9489,"Computer Science Department, University of Maryland, College Park, USA 20742",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Maryland; College Park; USA,4
6521,"Computer Science Department, University of Sao Paulo at Sao Carlos - Brazil",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Sao Paulo<ORG>; Sao Carlos - Brazil<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Sao Paulo; Sao Carlos - Brazil,3
8160,"Computer Science Department, University of Southern California, USA",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Southern California<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Southern California; USA,3
1314,"Computer Science Department, University of Stuttgart, Stuttgart, Germany",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Stuttgart<ORG>; Stuttgart<LOC>; Germany<LOC>,Computer Science Department; University of Stuttgart; Stuttgart; Germany,4
7872,"Computer Science Department, University of Twente, P.O. Box 217, 7500 AE Enschede, The Netherlands; E-mail: {grefen,vonk,apers}@cs.utwente.nl",Computer Science Department<ORG>; University of Twente<ORG>; P.O. Box<ORG>; AE Enschede<ORG>; The Netherlands<ORG>; E-mail<MISC>,Computer Science Department; University of Twente; P.O. Box; AE Enschede; The Netherlands; E-mail,6
8674,"Computer Science Department, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, USA 24060",Computer Science Department<ORG>; Virginia Tech<LOC>; Blacksburg<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Science Department; Virginia Tech; Blacksburg; USA,4
1673,"Computer Science Dept, UCLA",Computer Science Dept<MISC>; UCLA<ORG>,Computer Science Dept; UCLA,2
6754,"Computer Science Dept., Columbia University",Computer Science Dept<MISC>; Columbia University<ORG>,Computer Science Dept; Columbia University,2
6863,"Computer Science Dept., Stanford University, Stanford, CA",Computer Science Dept<MISC>; Stanford University<ORG>; Stanford<ORG>; CA<ORG>,Computer Science Dept; Stanford University; Stanford; CA,4
705,"Computer Science Dept., SUNY at Binghamton",Computer Science Dept<MISC>; SUNY<ORG>; Binghamton<LOC>,Computer Science Dept; SUNY; Binghamton,3
1836,"Computer Science Dept., UCLA, Los Angeles, CA",Computer Science Dept<MISC>; UCLA<ORG>; Los Angeles<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Computer Science Dept; UCLA; Los Angeles; CA,4
703,"Computer Science Dept., Univ. of Illinois at Chicago",Computer Science Dept<MISC>; Univ<LOC>; Illinois<LOC>; Chicago<LOC>,Computer Science Dept; Univ; Illinois; Chicago,4
6825,"Computer Science Division, National Technical University of Athens, 157 73 Athens, Greece",Computer Science Division<ORG>; National Technical University of Athens<ORG>; Athens<LOC>; Greece<LOC>,Computer Science Division; National Technical University of Athens; Athens; Greece,4
7279,"Computer Science Division, UC Berkeley",Computer Science Division<ORG>; UC Berkeley<ORG>,Computer Science Division; UC Berkeley,2
7466,"Computer Science Division, UC Berkeley, Berkeley, CA",Computer Science Division<ORG>; UC Berkeley<ORG>; Berkeley<ORG>; CA<ORG>,Computer Science Division; UC Berkeley; Berkeley; CA,4
6583,"Computer Science Program, School of EECS, University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL",Computer Science Program<MISC>; School of EECS<ORG>; University of Central Florida<ORG>; Orlando<LOC>; FL<LOC>,Computer Science Program; School of EECS; University of Central Florida; Orlando; FL,5
1858,"Computer Science UC, San Diego, La Jolla, CA",Computer Science UC<ORG>; San Diego<LOC>; La Jolla<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Computer Science UC; San Diego; La Jolla; CA,4
1812,"Computer Science, Department Hong Kong Univ. of Science and Technology, Hong Kong",Computer Science<ORG>; Department Hong Kong Univ<ORG>; Science and Technology<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Computer Science; Department Hong Kong Univ; Science and Technology; Hong Kong,4
851,"Computer Sciences Department - ICMC/USP, São Carlos, SP, Brazil",Computer Sciences Department - ICMC<ORG>; USP<LOC>; São Carlos<LOC>; SP<ORG>; Brazil<LOC>,Computer Sciences Department - ICMC; USP; São Carlos; SP; Brazil,5
6570,"Computer Sciences Department, University of Wisconsin-Madison",Computer Sciences Department<ORG>; University of Wisconsin-Madison<ORG>,Computer Sciences Department; University of Wisconsin-Madison,2
8684,"Computer Sciences Department, University of Wisconsin-Madison, Madison, USA 53706",Computer Sciences Department<ORG>; University of Wisconsin-Madison<ORG>; Madison<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Computer Sciences Department; University of Wisconsin-Madison; Madison; USA,4
616,"Computer Sciences Department, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI",Computer Sciences Department<ORG>; University of Wisconsin<ORG>; Madison<ORG>; WI<ORG>,Computer Sciences Department; University of Wisconsin; Madison; WI,4
6506,"Computer Sciences Dept., University of Wisconsin",Computer Sciences Dept<ORG>; University of Wisconsin<ORG>,Computer Sciences Dept; University of Wisconsin,2
1908,"Computer Sciences, Purdue University",Computer Sciences<ORG>; Purdue University<ORG>,Computer Sciences; Purdue University,2
3894,"Computer Technology Institute, Patras, Greece",Computer Technology Institute<ORG>; Patras<LOC>; Greece<LOC>,Computer Technology Institute; Patras; Greece,3
6524,"Computer Technology, Institute, P.O.Box 1122, GR-26110 Patras, Greece",Computer Technology<ORG>; Institute<ORG>; GR-26110 Patras<LOC>; Greece<LOC>,Computer Technology; Institute; GR-26110 Patras; Greece,4
783,"Computing Science, University of Aberdeen, Aberdeen, UK",Computing Science<ORG>; University of Aberdeen<ORG>; Aberdeen<LOC>; UK<LOC>,Computing Science; University of Aberdeen; Aberdeen; UK,4
4923,"Cornell Theory Center, Ithaca, NY",Cornell Theory Center<LOC>; Ithaca<LOC>; NY<LOC>,Cornell Theory Center; Ithaca; NY,3
9139,"Cornell University Ithaca, NY",Cornell University Ithaca<ORG>; NY<LOC>,Cornell University Ithaca; NY,2
4445,"Cornell University, Ithaca, New York",Cornell University<ORG>; Ithaca<LOC>; New York<LOC>,Cornell University; Ithaca; New York,3
2513,"Cornell University, Ithaca, NY",Cornell University<ORG>; Ithaca<LOC>; NY<LOC>,Cornell University; Ithaca; NY,3
5905,"Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, USA",Cornell University<ORG>; Ithaca<LOC>; NY<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Cornell University; Ithaca; NY; USA,4
6386,"Cornell University, Ithaca, USA",Cornell University<ORG>; Ithaca<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Cornell University; Ithaca; USA,3
9251,"Cornell University, Ithaca, USA 14853",Cornell University<ORG>; Ithaca<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Cornell University; Ithaca; USA,3
1053,"Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Department of Computer Science, New York University",Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences<ORG>; Department of Computer Science<ORG>; New York University<ORG>,Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences; Department of Computer Science; New York University,3
6772,"Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, New York University",Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences<ORG>; New York University<ORG>,Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences; New York University,2
6654,"Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, New York, University, New York, NY",Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences<ORG>; New York<LOC>; University<LOC>; NY<LOC>,Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences; New York; University; NY,5
7557,"Courant Institute, New York University",Courant Institute<ORG>; New York University<ORG>,Courant Institute; New York University,2
8226,"Courant Institute, New York, NY",Courant Institute<ORG>; New York<LOC>; NY<LOC>,Courant Institute; New York; NY,3
6680,"Courant Institute, NY",Courant Institute<ORG>; NY<ORG>,Courant Institute; NY,2
1026,"CS Dept., UCLA",CS Dept<ORG>; UCLA<ORG>,CS Dept; UCLA,2
789,"CS Storage Systems Dept., IBM Almaden Research Center",CS Storage Systems Dept<ORG>; IBM Almaden Research Center<ORG>,CS Storage Systems Dept; IBM Almaden Research Center,2
2131,"CSE, University of New South Wales, Sydney, Australia",CSE<ORG>; University of New South Wales<ORG>; Sydney<LOC>; Australia<LOC>,CSE; University of New South Wales; Sydney; Australia,4
8251,"CSIRO ICT Center/E-Health Research Center, Australia",CSIRO ICT Center<MISC>; E-Health Research Center<ORG>; Australia<LOC>,CSIRO ICT Center; E-Health Research Center; Australia,3
366,"CSIRO ICT Centre, North Ryde, NSW, Australia",CSIRO ICT Centre<MISC>; North Ryde<LOC>; NSW<LOC>; Australia<LOC>,CSIRO ICT Centre; North Ryde; NSW; Australia,4
3603,"CTI Patras, Greece",CTI Patras<ORG>; Greece<LOC>,CTI Patras; Greece,2
6637,"CTO, QUIQ, and Professor, UW-Madison",CTO<ORG>; QUIQ<ORG>; UW-Madison<ORG>,CTO; QUIQ; UW-Madison,3
3570,CWI,CWI<LOC>,CWI,1
466,"CWI Amsterdam, The Netherlands",CWI Amsterdam<LOC>; The Netherlands<ORG>,CWI Amsterdam; The Netherlands,2
5206,"CWI, Amsterdam, Netherlands",CWI<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; Netherlands<LOC>,CWI; Amsterdam; Netherlands,3
1002,"CWI, Amsterdam, The Netherlands",CWI<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; The Netherlands<LOC>,CWI; Amsterdam; The Netherlands,3
8614,"CWI, Amsterdam, The Netherlands 1098 SJ",CWI<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; The Netherlands 1098<LOC>; SJ<ORG>,CWI; Amsterdam; The Netherlands 1098; SJ,4
7762,"CWI, Kruislaan 413, 1098 SJ Amsterdam, The Netherlands; E-mail: {S.Manegold,M.L.Kersten}@cwi.nl","CWI<LOC>; Kruislaan<LOC>; SJ Amsterdam<ORG>; The Netherlands<ORG>; E-mail<MISC>; S.Manegold,M.L.Kersten}@cwi.nl<LOC>","CWI; Kruislaan; SJ Amsterdam; The Netherlands; E-mail; S.Manegold,M.L.Kersten}@cwi.nl",6
1223,"CWI, Kruislaan, GB Amsterdam, The Netherlands",CWI<LOC>; Kruislaan<LOC>; GB Amsterdam<LOC>; The Netherlands<ORG>,CWI; Kruislaan; GB Amsterdam; The Netherlands,4
1221,"CWI, Kruislaan, GB, Amsterdam, The Netherlands",CWI<LOC>; Kruislaan<LOC>; GB<LOC>; Amsterdam<LOC>; The Netherlands<LOC>,CWI; Kruislaan; GB; Amsterdam; The Netherlands,5
1885,"CWI, SJ Amsterdam, The Netherlands",CWI<LOC>; SJ Amsterdam<ORG>; The Netherlands<ORG>,CWI; SJ Amsterdam; The Netherlands,3
1353,"D.E.I.S. - Università della Calabria, Rende, Italy",D.E.I.S. - Università della Calabria<ORG>; Rende<LOC>; Italy<LOC>,D.E.I.S. - Università della Calabria; Rende; Italy,3
6664,"D.I.A., Università di Roma Tre",Università di Roma Tre<ORG>,Università di Roma Tre,1
6667,"D.I.F.A., Università della Basilicata",D.I.F.A.<MISC>; Università della Basilicata<ORG>,D.I.F.A.; Università della Basilicata,2
7763,"Data Distilleries B.V., Kruislaan 402, 1098 SM Amsterdam, The Netherlands; E-mail: P.Boncz@ddi.nl",Data Distilleries B.V.<MISC>; Kruislaan<LOC>; SM Amsterdam<ORG>; The Netherlands<ORG>; E-mail<MISC>,Data Distilleries B.V.; Kruislaan; SM Amsterdam; The Netherlands; E-mail,5
3571,"Data Distilleries, The Netherlands",Data Distilleries<MISC>; The Netherlands<ORG>,Data Distilleries; The Netherlands,2
6523,"Data Eng.Lab, Dept.of Informatic, Aristotic University, of Thessaloniki, GR-54006 Greece",Data Eng<PER>; Dept.of Informatic<MISC>; Aristotic University<ORG>; Thessaloniki<LOC>; GR-54006 Greece<MISC>,Data Eng; Dept.of Informatic; Aristotic University; Thessaloniki; GR-54006 Greece,5
6718,"Data Management Department, IBM T. J. Watson Research Center, P. O. Box 704, Yorktown Heights, NY",Data Management Department<ORG>; IBM<ORG>; P. O. Box<PER>; Yorktown Heights<ORG>; NY<LOC>,Data Management Department; IBM; P. O. Box; Yorktown Heights; NY,5
6574,"Data Management, IBM T. J. Watson Research Center, P. O.Box, 704, Yorktown Heights, NY",Data Management<MISC>; IBM<ORG>; P. O.Box<PER>; Yorktown Heights<ORG>; NY<LOC>,Data Management; IBM; P. O.Box; Yorktown Heights; NY,5
347,"Data Mining Technologies, Oracle",Data Mining Technologies<ORG>; Oracle<ORG>,Data Mining Technologies; Oracle,2
979,"Database and Artificial Intelligence Group, Technische Universität, Wien, Vienna, Austria",Database<MISC>; Artificial Intelligence Group<ORG>; Technische Universität<ORG>; Wien<LOC>; Vienna<LOC>; Austria<LOC>,Database; Artificial Intelligence Group; Technische Universität; Wien; Vienna; Austria,6
1640,"Database Research Group, Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (ETH), Zurich, Switzerland",Database Research Group<ORG>; Swiss Federal Institute of Technology<ORG>; ETH<LOC>; Zurich<LOC>; Switzerland<LOC>,Database Research Group; Swiss Federal Institute of Technology; ETH; Zurich; Switzerland,5
9756,"Database Security Oracle Corp., Redwood City, CA",Database Security Oracle Corp<MISC>; Redwood City<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Database Security Oracle Corp; Redwood City; CA,3
7021,"Database Systems Lab, Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India",Database Systems Lab<MISC>; Indian Institute of Science<ORG>; Bangalore<LOC>; India<LOC>,Database Systems Lab; Indian Institute of Science; Bangalore; India,4
6476,"Database Systems Lab, SERC, Indian Institue of science, Bangalore 560012,INDIA, Lucent Bell Labs, 600 Mountain Avenue, Murray Hill, NJ",Database Systems Lab<MISC>; SERC<ORG>; Indian Institue of science<ORG>; Bangalore<PER>; Lucent Bell Labs<ORG>; Mountain Avenue<LOC>; Murray Hill<LOC>; NJ<MISC>,Database Systems Lab; SERC; Indian Institue of science; Bangalore; Lucent Bell Labs; Mountain Avenue; Murray Hill; NJ,8
1306,"Database Systems Lab, SERC, Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India",Database Systems Lab<MISC>; SERC<ORG>; Indian Institute of Science<ORG>; Bangalore<LOC>; India<LOC>,Database Systems Lab; SERC; Indian Institute of Science; Bangalore; India,5
2142,"Database Systems Lab, SERC/CSA, Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India",Database Systems Lab<MISC>; SERC<ORG>; CSA<ORG>; Indian Institute of Science<ORG>; Bangalore<LOC>; India<LOC>,Database Systems Lab; SERC; CSA; Indian Institute of Science; Bangalore; India,6
1127,"Database Systems Lab., SERC, Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India",Database Systems Lab<MISC>; SERC<ORG>; Indian Institute of Science<ORG>; Bangalore<LOC>; India<LOC>,Database Systems Lab; SERC; Indian Institute of Science; Bangalore; India,5
7827,"Database Systems R& D Center, University of Florida, Gainesville, FL 32611––6125, USA; E-mail: su@cise.ufl.edu",Database Systems R& D Center<MISC>; University of Florida<ORG>; Gainesville<LOC>; FL 32611––6125<LOC>; USA<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>,Database Systems R& D Center; University of Florida; Gainesville; FL 32611––6125; USA; E-mail,6
1284,"Databases and Distributed Systems Group, Department of Computer Science, Darmstadt University of Technology - Darmstadt, Germany",Distributed Systems Group<ORG>; Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Darmstadt University of Technology - Darmstadt<ORG>; Germany<LOC>,Distributed Systems Group; Department of Computer Science; Darmstadt University of Technology - Darmstadt; Germany,4
8748,"David R. Cheriton School of Computer Science, University of Waterloo, Waterloo, Canada",David R. Cheriton<PER>; University of Waterloo<ORG>; Waterloo<MISC>; Canada<LOC>,David R. Cheriton; University of Waterloo; Waterloo; Canada,4
597,"David R. Cheriton School of Computer Science, University of Waterloo, Waterloo, Ontario, Canada",David R. Cheriton<PER>; University of Waterloo<ORG>; Waterloo<LOC>; Ontario<LOC>; Canada<LOC>,David R. Cheriton; University of Waterloo; Waterloo; Ontario; Canada,5
4258,"DEI, Politecnico di Milano, Italy",DEI<ORG>; Politecnico di Milano<LOC>; Italy<LOC>,DEI; Politecnico di Milano; Italy,3
1625,Deis UNICAL,Deis UNICAL<ORG>,Deis UNICAL,1
7657,"DEIS---CSITE--CNR, University of Bologna, Bologna, Italy",DEIS---CSITE<MISC>; CNR<ORG>; University of Bologna<ORG>; Bologna<LOC>; Italy<LOC>,DEIS---CSITE; CNR; University of Bologna; Bologna; Italy,5
9244,"DEIS, Università della Calabria, Rende (CS), Italy",DEIS<ORG>; Università della Calabria<ORG>; Rende<LOC>; CS<LOC>; Italy<LOC>,DEIS; Università della Calabria; Rende; CS; Italy,5
9366,"Department of Anthropology, UCR, Riverside, USA",Department of Anthropology<ORG>; UCR<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Anthropology; UCR; Riverside; USA,4
758,"Department of Anthropology, University of California - Riverside, Riverside, CA",Department of Anthropology<ORG>; University of California - Riverside<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Department of Anthropology; University of California - Riverside; Riverside; CA,4
8237,"Department of Biology, Indiana University, USA",Department of Biology<ORG>; Indiana University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Biology; Indiana University; USA,3
8136,"Department of Computer and Information Science, Moore School Building, University of Pennsylvania, USA",Department of Computer and Information Science<ORG>; Moore School Building<ORG>; University of Pennsylvania<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Science; Moore School Building; University of Pennsylvania; USA,4
1480,"Department of Computer and Information Science, The University of Michigan - Dearborn, Dearborn, MI",Department of Computer and Information Science<ORG>; The University of Michigan - Dearborn<ORG>; Dearborn<LOC>; MI<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Science; The University of Michigan - Dearborn; Dearborn; MI,4
8019,"Department of Computer and Information Science, The University of Michigan - Dearborn, MI 48128, Dearborn, USA",Department of Computer and Information Science<ORG>; The University of Michigan - Dearborn<ORG>; MI 48128<LOC>; Dearborn<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Science; The University of Michigan - Dearborn; MI 48128; Dearborn; USA,5
8677,"Department of Computer and Information Science, University of Michigan, Dearborn, USA 48128",Department of Computer and Information Science<ORG>; University of Michigan<ORG>; Dearborn<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Science; University of Michigan; Dearborn; USA,4
1550,"Department of Computer and Information Sciences and Engineering, University of Florida, Gainesville, FL",Department of Computer and Information Sciences and Engineering<ORG>; University of Florida<ORG>; Gainesville<LOC>; FL<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Sciences and Engineering; University of Florida; Gainesville; FL,4
8586,"Department of Computer and Information Sciences and Engineering, University of Florida, Gainsville, USA",Department of Computer and Information Sciences and Engineering<ORG>; University of Florida<ORG>; Gainsville<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Sciences and Engineering; University of Florida; Gainsville; USA,4
8831,"Department of Computer and Information Sciences, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, USA 19104",Department of Computer and Information Sciences<ORG>; University of Pennsylvania<ORG>; Philadelphia<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer and Information Sciences; University of Pennsylvania; Philadelphia; USA,4
8381,"Department of Computer Engineering & Maths, Rovira i Virgili University of Tarragona, Catalonia",Department of Computer Engineering & Maths<ORG>; Rovira<ORG>; Virgili University of Tarragona<ORG>; Catalonia<LOC>,Department of Computer Engineering & Maths; Rovira; Virgili University of Tarragona; Catalonia,4
7935,"Department of Computer Engineering and Information Technology, City University of Hong Kong, Tat Chee Avenue, Kowloon, Hong Kong, China",Department of Computer Engineering and Information Technology<ORG>; City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Tat Chee Avenue<LOC>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Engineering and Information Technology; City University of Hong Kong; Tat Chee Avenue; Kowloon; Hong Kong; China,6
7993,"Department of Computer Engineering, Bilkent University, 06800, Bilkent, Ankara, Turkey",Department of Computer Engineering<ORG>; Bilkent University<ORG>; Bilkent<LOC>; Ankara<LOC>; Turkey<LOC>,Department of Computer Engineering; Bilkent University; Bilkent; Ankara; Turkey,5
2188,"Department of Computer Engineering, Bilkent University, Ankara, Turkey",Department of Computer Engineering<ORG>; Bilkent University<ORG>; Ankara<LOC>; Turkey<LOC>,Department of Computer Engineering; Bilkent University; Ankara; Turkey,4
8544,"Department of Computer Engineering, Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea 702-701",Department of Computer Engineering<ORG>; Kyungpook National University<ORG>; Daegu<LOC>; South Korea<LOC>,Department of Computer Engineering; Kyungpook National University; Daegu; South Korea,4
8155,"Department of Computer Engineering, Middle East Technical University, Turkey",Department of Computer Engineering<ORG>; Middle East Technical University<ORG>; Turkey<LOC>,Department of Computer Engineering; Middle East Technical University; Turkey,3
2091,"Department of Computer Science & Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of Toronto",Department of Computer Science & Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering<ORG>; University of Toronto<ORG>,Department of Computer Science & Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering; University of Toronto,2
8165,"Department of Computer Science & Electrical Engineering, University of Maryland, USA",Department of Computer Science & Electrical Engineering<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science & Electrical Engineering; University of Maryland; USA,3
755,"Department of Computer Science & Engineering, University of California - Riverside, Riverside, CA",Department of Computer Science & Engineering<ORG>; University of California - Riverside<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; CA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science & Engineering; University of California - Riverside; Riverside; CA,4
8170,"Department of Computer Science & Engineering, University of California Riverside, USA",Department of Computer Science & Engineering<ORG>; University of California Riverside<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science & Engineering; University of California Riverside; USA,3
8542,"Department of Computer Science and Advanced Information Technology Research Center (AITrc), Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), Daejeon, South Korea 305-701",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; AITrc<LOC>; Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology<ORG>; KAIST<ORG>; Daejeon<LOC>; South Korea<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; AITrc; Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology; KAIST; Daejeon; South Korea,6
1158,"Department of Computer Science and Advanced Information Technology Research Center (AITrc), Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), Taejon, Korea",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; AITrc<LOC>; Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology<ORG>; KAIST<ORG>; Taejon<LOC>; Korea<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; AITrc; Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology; KAIST; Taejon; Korea,6
998,"Department of Computer Science and Automation, Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore, India",Department of Computer Science and Automation<ORG>; Indian Institute of Science<ORG>; Bangalore<LOC>; India<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Automation; Indian Institute of Science; Bangalore; India,4
8144,"Department of Computer Science and Automation, Technical University of Ilmenau, Germany",Department of Computer Science and Automation<ORG>; Technical University of Ilmenau<ORG>; Germany<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Automation; Technical University of Ilmenau; Germany,3
8511,"Department of Computer Science and Computer Engineering, La Trobe University, Australia",Department of Computer Science and Computer Engineering<ORG>; La Trobe University<MISC>; Australia<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Computer Engineering; La Trobe University; Australia,3
2093,"Department of Computer Science and Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of Toronto",Department of Computer Science and Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering<ORG>; University of Toronto<ORG>,Department of Computer Science and Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering; University of Toronto,2
7992,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Arizona State University, AZ 85287-5406, Tempe, USA",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Arizona State University<ORG>; AZ<ORG>; Tempe<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Arizona State University; AZ; Tempe; USA,5
1656,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Arizona State University,Tempe, AZ",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Arizona State University<ORG>; Tempe<ORG>; AZ<ORG>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Arizona State University; Tempe; AZ,4
8150,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Bourns College of Engineering, University of California, Riverside, USA",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Bourns College of Engineering<ORG>; University of California<ORG>; Riverside<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Bourns College of Engineering; University of California; Riverside; USA,5
7721,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Box 352350, University of Washington, Seattle, WA 98195-2350, USA; e-mail: {zives,alon,weld}@cs.washington.edu",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Box 352350<MISC>; University of Washington<ORG>; Seattle<LOC>; WA<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Box 352350; University of Washington; Seattle; WA; USA,6
8687,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong, China",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Chinese University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong; China,4
8804,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Chinese University of Hong Kong, New Territories, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; New Territories<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Chinese University of Hong Kong; New Territories; Hong Kong,4
540,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Sha Tin, New Territories, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Sha Tin<LOC>; New Territories<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Chinese University of Hong Kong; Sha Tin; New Territories; Hong Kong,5
8173,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Helsinki University of Technology, Finland",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Helsinki University of Technology<ORG>; Finland<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Helsinki University of Technology; Finland,3
1276,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology Bombay, Mumbai, India",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Indian Institute of Technology Bombay<ORG>; Mumbai<LOC>; India<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Indian Institute of Technology Bombay; Mumbai; India,4
6909,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology Bombay, Mumbai, India 400076",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Indian Institute of Technology Bombay<ORG>; Mumbai<LOC>; India<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Indian Institute of Technology Bombay; Mumbai; India,4
1479,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Michigan State University<ORG>; East Lansing<LOC>; MI<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Michigan State University; East Lansing; MI,4
1431,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, State University of New York at Buffalo, Buffalo, NY",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; State University of New York<ORG>; Buffalo<LOC>; NY<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; State University of New York; Buffalo; NY,5
7747,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong; e-mail: adafu@cse.cuhk.edu.hk",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; Chinese University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; Chinese University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong,3
8612,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Kowloon, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<MISC>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Kowloon; Hong Kong,4
9385,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Kowloon, Hong Kong, China",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<MISC>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Kowloon; Hong Kong; China,5
8355,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Ohio State University, USA",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; The Ohio State University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; The Ohio State University; USA,3
859,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; The Pennsylvania State University<ORG>; University Park<ORG>; PA<ORG>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; The Pennsylvania State University; University Park; PA,4
7665,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA 16802, USA; e-mail: &lcub;gurumurt,anand,vijay,kandemir,mji&rcub;&commat;cse.psu.edu",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; The Pennsylvania State University<ORG>; University Park<ORG>; PA 16802<LOC>; USA<LOC>; mji&rcub;&commat;cse.psu.edu<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; The Pennsylvania State University; University Park; PA 16802; USA; mji&rcub;&commat;cse.psu.edu,6
725,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; University of Minnesota<ORG>; Minneapolis<LOC>; MN<ORG>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; University of Minnesota; Minneapolis; MN,4
960,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Minnesota, Minnesota, MN",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; University of Minnesota<ORG>; Minnesota<LOC>; MN<ORG>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; University of Minnesota; Minnesota; MN,4
9467,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Washington, Seattle, USA",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; University of Washington<ORG>; Seattle<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; University of Washington; Seattle; USA,4
7867,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Washington, Seattle, WA, 98195; E-mail: alon@cs.washington.edu",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; University of Washington<ORG>; Seattle<LOC>; WA<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>; alon@cs.washington.edu<MISC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; University of Washington; Seattle; WA; E-mail; alon@cs.washington.edu,6
7948,"Department of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Washington, WA 98195, Seattle, USA",Department of Computer Science and Engineering<ORG>; University of Washington<ORG>; WA 98195<LOC>; Seattle<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Engineering; University of Washington; WA 98195; Seattle; USA,5
6969,"Department of Computer Science and Information Engineering, National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan, ROC",Department of Computer Science and Information Engineering<ORG>; National Taiwan University<ORG>; Taipei<LOC>; Taiwan<LOC>; ROC<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Information Engineering; National Taiwan University; Taipei; Taiwan; ROC,5
1527,"Department of Computer Science and Information Systems, University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science and Information Systems<ORG>; University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Information Systems; University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong,3
9351,"Department of Computer Science and Software Engineering, ARC Centre for Perceptive and Intelligent Machines in Complex Environments, The University of Melbourne, Melbourne, Australia",Department of Computer Science and Software Engineering<ORG>; ARC Centre for Perceptive and Intelligent Machines in Complex Environments<ORG>; The University of Melbourne<ORG>; Melbourne<LOC>; Australia<LOC>,Department of Computer Science and Software Engineering; ARC Centre for Perceptive and Intelligent Machines in Complex Environments; The University of Melbourne; Melbourne; Australia,5
1726,"Department of Computer Science Northeastern University, Liaoning, China",Department of Computer Science Northeastern University<ORG>; Liaoning<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science Northeastern University; Liaoning; China,3
6569,"Department of Computer Science University of Maryland, College Park, Also with the Institute for Advanced Computer Studies, University Maryland",Department of Computer Science University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<ORG>; Institute for Advanced Computer Studies<ORG>; University Maryland<ORG>,Department of Computer Science University of Maryland; College Park; Institute for Advanced Computer Studies; University Maryland,4
6568,"Department of Computer Science University of Maryland, College Park, Also with the Institute for Systems Research, University of Maryland",Department of Computer Science University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<ORG>; Institute for Systems Research<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>,Department of Computer Science University of Maryland; College Park; Institute for Systems Research; University of Maryland,4
7786,"Department of Computer Science, Aalborg University 9220 Aalborg Øst, Denmark; E-mail: {simas,csj}@cs.auc.dk",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Aalborg University<ORG>; Denmark<LOC>; E-mail<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Aalborg University; Denmark; E-mail,4
1595,"Department of Computer Science, Aalborg University, Aalborg Ø, Denmark",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Aalborg University<ORG>; Aalborg Ø<LOC>; Denmark<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Aalborg University; Aalborg Ø; Denmark,4
9360,"Department of Computer Science, Aalborg University, Aalborg, Denmark",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Aalborg University<ORG>; Aalborg<LOC>; Denmark<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Aalborg University; Aalborg; Denmark,4
1476,"Department of Computer Science, Aalborg University, Denmark",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Aalborg University<ORG>; Denmark<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Aalborg University; Denmark,3
7980,"Department of Computer Science, Aalborg University, Fredrik Bajers Vej 7E, 9220, Aalborg Øst, Denmark",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Aalborg University<ORG>; Fredrik Bajers<ORG>; Aalborg Øst<LOC>; Denmark<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Aalborg University; Fredrik Bajers; Aalborg Øst; Denmark,5
8171,"Department of Computer Science, Boston University, Boston, MA 02215, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Boston University<ORG>; Boston<ORG>; MA 02215<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Boston University; Boston; MA 02215; USA,5
8151,"Department of Computer Science, Boston University, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Boston University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Boston University; USA,3
7916,"Department of Computer Science, Brandeis University, MA 02254, Waltham, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Brandeis University<ORG>; MA 02254<ORG>; Waltham<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Brandeis University; MA 02254; Waltham; USA,5
8087,"Department of Computer Science, Brandeis University, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Brandeis University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Brandeis University; USA,3
1533,"Department of Computer Science, Brandeis University, Waltham, MA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Brandeis University<ORG>; Waltham<ORG>; MA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Brandeis University; Waltham; MA,4
7917,"Department of Computer Science, Brown University, RI 02912, Providence, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Brown University<ORG>; RI 02912<ORG>; Providence<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Brown University; RI 02912; Providence; USA,5
8085,"Department of Computer Science, Brown University, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Brown University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Brown University; USA,3
8502,"Department of Computer Science, Center for Automation Research Institute for Advanced Computer Studies, University of Maryland, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Center for Automation Research Institute for Advanced Computer Studies<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Center for Automation Research Institute for Advanced Computer Studies; University of Maryland; USA,4
6967,"Department of Computer Science, City University of Hong Kong, 83 Tat Chee Avenue, Kowloon, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; City University of Hong Kong; Kowloon; Hong Kong,4
1522,"Department of Computer Science, City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; City University of Hong Kong; Hong Kong,3
762,"Department of Computer Science, City University of Hong Kong, Kowloon Tong, Hong Kong SAR, China",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Kowloon Tong<LOC>; Hong Kong SAR<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; City University of Hong Kong; Kowloon Tong; Hong Kong SAR; China,5
1274,"Department of Computer Science, City University of Hong Kong, Kowloon, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; City University of Hong Kong<ORG>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; City University of Hong Kong; Kowloon; Hong Kong,4
1103,"Department of Computer Science, Darmstadt University of Technology",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Darmstadt University of Technology<ORG>,Department of Computer Science; Darmstadt University of Technology,2
8571,"Department of Computer Science, Drop and Statistics, University of São Paulo at São Carlos, São Carlos, Brazil",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Drop and Statistics<MISC>; University of São Paulo<ORG>; São Carlos<LOC>; Brazil<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Drop and Statistics; University of São Paulo; São Carlos; Brazil,6
1067,"Department of Computer Science, Duke University, Durham, NC",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Duke University<ORG>; Durham<ORG>; NC<ORG>,Department of Computer Science; Duke University; Durham; NC,4
8510,"Department of Computer Science, Fudan University, China",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Fudan University<ORG>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Fudan University; China,3
9332,"Department of Computer Science, Global Scientific Information and Computing Center, Tokyo Institute of Technology, Tokyo, Japan 152-8552",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Global Scientific Information and Computing Center<MISC>; Tokyo Institute of Technology<ORG>; Tokyo<LOC>; Japan<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Global Scientific Information and Computing Center; Tokyo Institute of Technology; Tokyo; Japan,5
9306,"Department of Computer Science, Harbin Institute of Technology, Harbin, China",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Harbin Institute of Technology<ORG>; Harbin<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Harbin Institute of Technology; Harbin; China,4
1034,"Department of Computer Science, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Clear Water Bay, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<ORG>; Clear Water Bay<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Clear Water Bay; Hong Kong,4
7811,"Department of Computer Science, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Clear Water Bay, Kowloon, China; e-mail: luhj&commat;cs.ust.hk",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<ORG>; Clear Water Bay<ORG>; Kowloon<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Clear Water Bay; Kowloon; China,5
1525,"Department of Computer Science, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Clearwater Bay, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<ORG>; Clearwater Bay<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Clearwater Bay; Hong Kong,4
516,"Department of Computer Science, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Hong Kong",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<ORG>; Hong Kong<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Hong Kong,3
8683,"Department of Computer Science, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Kowloon, Hong Kong, China",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology<ORG>; Kowloon<LOC>; Hong Kong<LOC>; China<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Hong Kong University of Science and Technology; Kowloon; Hong Kong; China,5
7745,"Department of Computer Science, Institute for Advanced Computer Studies & Institute for Systems Research, University of Maryland, College Park, MD 20742, USA; e-mail: {elemar,vs}@cs.umd.edu",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Institute for Advanced Computer Studies & Institute for Systems Research<ORG>; University of Maryland<ORG>; College Park<ORG>; MD 20742<MISC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Institute for Advanced Computer Studies & Institute for Systems Research; University of Maryland; College Park; MD 20742; USA,6
8890,"Department of Computer Science, Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), Daejeon, South Korea",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology<ORG>; KAIST<ORG>; Daejeon<LOC>; South Korea<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology; KAIST; Daejeon; South Korea,5
8012,"Department of Computer Science, Monmouth University, NJ 07764, West Long Branch, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Monmouth University<ORG>; NJ 07764<ORG>; West Long Branch<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Monmouth University; NJ 07764; West Long Branch; USA,5
9345,"Department of Computer Science, National Chengchi University, Taipei, Taiwan, ROC",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National Chengchi University<ORG>; Taipei<LOC>; Taiwan<LOC>; ROC<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; National Chengchi University; Taipei; Taiwan; ROC,5
8802,"Department of Computer Science, National Chiao Tung University, Hsinchu, Taiwan, ROC",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National Chiao Tung University<ORG>; Hsinchu<LOC>; Taiwan<LOC>; ROC<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; National Chiao Tung University; Hsinchu; Taiwan; ROC,5
9343,"Department of Computer Science, National Tsing Hua University, Hsinchu, Taiwan, ROC",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National Tsing Hua University<ORG>; Hsinchu<LOC>; Taiwan<LOC>; ROC<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; National Tsing Hua University; Hsinchu; Taiwan; ROC,5
1914,"Department of Computer Science, National University of Singapore",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National University of Singapore<ORG>,Department of Computer Science; National University of Singapore,2
8013,"Department of Computer Science, National University of Singapore, 3 Science Drive 2, 117543, Singapore",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National University of Singapore<ORG>; 3 Science Drive 2<MISC>; Singapore<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; National University of Singapore; 3 Science Drive 2; Singapore,4
6723,"Department of Computer Science, National University of Singapore, 3 Science Drive 2, Singapore",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National University of Singapore<ORG>; 3 Science Drive 2<MISC>; Singapore<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; National University of Singapore; 3 Science Drive 2; Singapore,4
7768,"Department of Computer Science, National University of Singapore, 3 Science Drive 2, Singapore 117543; E-mail: tankl@comp.nus.edu.sg",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; National University of Singapore<ORG>; 3 Science Drive 2<MISC>; Singapore<LOC>; E-mail<MISC>; tankl@comp.nus.edu.sg<MISC>,Department of Computer Science; National University of Singapore; 3 Science Drive 2; Singapore; E-mail; tankl@comp.nus.edu.sg,6
8379,"Department of Computer Science, Purdue University, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Purdue University<ORG>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Purdue University; USA,3
727,"Department of Computer Science, Purdue University, West Lafayette, IN",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Purdue University<ORG>; West Lafayette<ORG>; IN<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Purdue University; West Lafayette; IN,4
8800,"Department of Computer Science, Purdue University, West Lafayette, USA 47907",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Purdue University<ORG>; West Lafayette<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Purdue University; West Lafayette; USA,4
7888,"Department of Computer Science, Southwest Texas State University, San Marcos, TX 78666 USA; e-mail: angu@swt.edu",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Southwest Texas State University<ORG>; San Marcos<LOC>; TX 78666<MISC>; angu@swt.edu<MISC>,Department of Computer Science; Southwest Texas State University; San Marcos; TX 78666; angu@swt.edu,5
8055,"Department of Computer Science, SUNY at Binghamton, USA",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; SUNY<ORG>; Binghamton<LOC>; USA<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; SUNY; Binghamton; USA,4
1115,"Department of Computer Science, Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (ETHZ), ETH Zentrum, Zürich, Switzerland",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Swiss Federal Institute of Technology<ORG>; ETHZ<LOC>; ETH Zentrum<ORG>; Zürich<LOC>; Switzerland<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Swiss Federal Institute of Technology; ETHZ; ETH Zentrum; Zürich; Switzerland,6
1055,"Department of Computer Science, The Technion, Haifa, Israel",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; The Technion<ORG>; Haifa<LOC>; Israel<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; The Technion; Haifa; Israel,4
9330,"Department of Computer Science, Tokyo Institute of Technology, Tokyo, Japan 152-8552",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; Tokyo Institute of Technology<ORG>; Tokyo<LOC>; Japan<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; Tokyo Institute of Technology; Tokyo; Japan,4
6775,"Department of Computer Science, University of Arizona, AZ",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of Arizona<ORG>; AZ<ORG>,Department of Computer Science; University of Arizona; AZ,3
1483,"Department of Computer Science, University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of Arizona<ORG>; Tucson<LOC>; AZ<ORG>,Department of Computer Science; University of Arizona; Tucson; AZ,4
1734,"Department of Computer Science, University of British Columbia",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of British Columbia<ORG>,Department of Computer Science; University of British Columbia,2
6496,"Department of Computer Science, University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC V6T 1Z4 Canada",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of British Columbia<ORG>; Vancouver<LOC>; BC V6T 1Z4 Canada<MISC>,Department of Computer Science; University of British Columbia; Vancouver; BC V6T 1Z4 Canada,4
8695,"Department of Computer Science, University of Calgary, Calgary, Canada",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of Calgary<ORG>; Calgary<LOC>; Canada<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; University of Calgary; Calgary; Canada,4
8154,"Department of Computer Science, University of Calgary, Canada",Department of Computer Science<ORG>; University of Calgary<ORG>; Canada<LOC>,Department of Computer Science; University of Calgary; Canada,3
